popcultcha.com.au 2011-06-18

# Buy Collectables, Action Figures, T-Shirts, True Blood & Pop Culture Merchandise from Popcultcha Australia

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Popcultcha respects the privacy rights of all our customers with whom we conduct business. In compliance with the obligations under the Privacy Act 1998 as amended by the Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000, we have implemented stringent security measures and procedures so that you can be assured that your personal information remains secure and confidential.

Popcultcha will generally only collect personal information where it is necessary for conducting business and providing services to our customers. This may be through actual personal contact at our Card Mania store in Geelong, Australia, or in correspondence via telephone, mail, email or facsimile. The personal information provided to us via the completion of our on-line form will also be collected.

Popcultcha uses per-session cookies to monitor the use of our secure services site. This occurs only when you have logged onto Popcultcha by using your "username" and "password" and is only done for the purpose of monitoring transactions, the contents of your shopping basket, whether you incur GST and generally maintaining security. We do not use cookies for any other purpose or in any other context and you can be assured that the cookies used will not be to the detriment of your computer or your on-line shopping experience.

Popcultcha does not disclose your personal information to third parties for purely marketing purposes. The personal information held by Popcultcha is generally kept confidential, however we may be required to disclose personal information to certain third parties.

Popcultcha may occasionally use or disclose your personal information for a purpose other than the primary purpose for which it is collected. This may be where it is required by law or where you would reasonably expect such use, including but not limited to:

  * Providing information to you about our new products or services, unless you have instructed us not to do so;
  * Internal research, planning, accounting and administrative purposes;
  * For reasonable financial, auditing or quality compliance purposes; and
  * Any other situation required by law.

 **SECURITY MEASURES**

Your on-line shopping experience with Popcultcha is both safe and secure as we use Secure Socket Layers (SSL) 128-bit data encryption to protect your personal information and credit card details from being intercepted by any unauthorised parties, loss or misuse whilst under our control.

When using Popcultcha, or any on-line store, always look for the padlock icon at the bottom of your browser before transmitting your credit card details.

At Popcultcha, we recognise the growing risk of fraudulent on-line credit card transactions and we make every effort to reduce credit risk and credit card misuse. In line with this policy, we reserve the right to contact our customers to request further credit card verification.
